<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Google / query: antibiotics / results: 30 -->
<searchresult>
<document><title>Antibiotics - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><snippet>An antibiotic is an agent that either kills or inhibits the growth of a microorganism. The term antibiotic was first used in 1942 by Selman Waksman and his ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>What Are Antibiotics? - Medical News Today</title><snippet>24 lis 2013 - Antibiotics, also known as antibacterials, are types of medications that destroy or slow down the growth of bacteria. The Greek word anti means ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotics: MedlinePlus</title><snippet>Antibiotics are powerful medicines that fight bacterial infections. Used properly, antibiotics can save lives. They either kill bacteria or keep them from reproducing ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotics. Side Effects &amp; Types of Antibiotics | Patient.co.uk</title><snippet>Antibiotics are a group of medicines that are used to treat infections caused by bacteria and certain parasites. They do not work against infections that are ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotics: Learn What Infections these Medications Treat</title><snippet>Antibiotics are frequently prescribed to a person with an infection. There are over 100 antibiotics. The choice of an antibiotic to treat an infection depends on the ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotics: Misuse puts you and others at risk - Mayo Clinic</title><snippet>Antibiotic resistance occurs when antibiotics no longer work against disease-causing bacteria. These infections are difficult to treat and can mean longer lasting ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>HowStuffWorks "How do antibiotics work?"</title><snippet>Before we had antibiotics, there were few choices when it came to treating infections: You could wait and see if the infection improved on its own, or you could ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotic definition - Medical Dictionary: Definitions of ...</title><snippet>Antibiotic: A drug used to treat bacterial infections. Antibiotics have no effect on viral infections. Originally, an antibiotic was a substance produced by one ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotics - NHS Choices</title><snippet>Find everything you need to know about antibiotics including causes, symptoms, diagnosis and treatment, with links to other useful resources.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Get Smart: Know When Antibiotics Work - Centers for ...</title><snippet>9 kwi 2014 - Antibiotics cure bacterial infections, not viral infections such as: Colds or flu;; Most coughs and bronchitis;; Sore throats not caused by strep; or ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Frequently Asked Questions About Antibiotic Resistance ...</title><snippet>14 kwi 2014 - The germs that contaminate food can be resistant because of the use of antibiotics in people and in food animals. We can prevent many of ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Sustainable Table | Antibiotics</title><snippet>Factory farms administer antibiotics to farm animals to promote growth and compensate for filthy conditions. Learn how this threatens human health.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Alliance for the Prudent Use of Antibiotics - Tufts University</title><snippet>The Alliance for the Prudent Use of Antibiotics (APUA) has been the leading global non-governmental organization fighting to preserve the effectiveness of ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Johns Hopkins Guides: Johns Hopkins ABX Guide ...</title><snippet>The Johns Hopkins Guides provide up-to-date, evidence-based ABX (antibiotic), HIV, and Diabetes Guides on iPhone, iPad, Android, BlackBerry, and Window ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Johns Hopkins Guides: Antibiotic (ABX), HIV, &amp; Diabetes ...</title><snippet>Official website of the Johns Hopkins Guides -- Antibiotic (ABX), HIV &amp; Diabetes Guides, powered by Unbound Medicine. Download to iPhone, iPad, Android, ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>antibiotic: Definition from Answers.com</title><snippet>antibiotic n. A substance, such as penicillin or streptomycin, produced by or derived from certain fungi, bacteria, and other organisms, that can destroy.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>European Antibiotic Awareness Day - ECDC</title><snippet>A number of initiatives are taking place across Europe to spread the messages on the risks associated with inappropriate use of antibiotics and how to take ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Fatal Superbugs: Antibiotics Losing Effectiveness, WHO Says</title><snippet>1 maj 2014 - Many bacterial infections, such as gonorrhea (microscopic image above), are no longer easily treated with antibiotics. PHOTOGRAPH BY ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotics - Health News - The New York Times</title><snippet>A free collection of articles about antibiotics published in The New York Times.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotics | An Open Access Journal from MDPI - MDPI.com</title><snippet>Antibiotics, an international, peer-reviewed Open Access journal.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>The Journal of Antibiotics - Nature</title><snippet>Journal of Antibiotics, official journal of the Japan Antibiotics Research Association, is a print and online publication that focuses on research on antibiotics and ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Keep Antibiotics Working</title><snippet>Doctors depend on antibiotics to treat illnesses caused by bacteria, from pneumonia to meningitis and other life-threatening infections. The effectiveness of many ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotics news, articles and information: - Natural News</title><snippet>5/2/2014 12:31:22 PM - A new report issued by the World Health Organization denounces the current overuse of antibiotics and is saying that antibiotics now ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotics Used to Treat Acne - Dermatology - About.com</title><snippet>Antibiotics are frequently used to treat acne. This article gives a profile of some of the most commonly prescribed antibiotics for acne.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotics Attack | HHMI.org</title><snippet>Antibiotics Attack has been removed from our site. Please update your bookmarks.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Imagining the Post-Antibiotics Future — Editor's Picks ...</title><snippet>10 lut 2014 - After 85 years, antibiotics are growing impotent. So what will medicine, agriculture and everyday life look like if we l…</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Preserving Antibiotics, Rationally — NEJM</title><snippet>26 gru 2013 - Perspective from The New England Journal of Medicine — Preserving Antibiotics, Rationally.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>WHO | WHO's first global report on antibiotic resistance ...</title><snippet>30 April 2014 | Geneva - A new report by WHO–its first to look at antimicrobial resistance, including antibiotic resistance, globally–reveals that this serious threat ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Antibiotic Resistance - The Telegraph</title><snippet>Antibiotics have transformed human health and saved millions of lives. Now, as a result of overuse, they are no longer working. The golden age of medicine has ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>AntibioticAwareness.ca</title><snippet>Health Care Providers. Healthcare providers have an important role to play in reducing antibiotic resistance. This section provides materials to use with your ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
</searchresult>