<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Google / query: silicon valley / results: 30 -->
<searchresult>
<document><title>Silicon Valley (TV Series 2014– ) - IMDb</title><snippet>In the high-tech gold rush of modern Silicon Valley, the people most qualified to succeed are the least capable of handling success. A comedy partially inspired ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley (TV series) - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><snippet>Silicon Valley is an American sitcom that centers on six tech-geeks who are living ... In 1987 he moved to the Silicon Valley region of Northern California and ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Dolina Krzemowa – Wikipedia, wolna encyklopedia</title><snippet>Dolina Krzemowa (ang. Silicon Valley) – nazwa nadana północnej części Doliny Santa Clara, która znajduje się w północnej części amerykańskiego stanu ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title><snippet>Silicon Valley is a nickname for the South Bay portion of the San Francisco Bay Area in Northern California, United States. It is home to many of the world's ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley | Homepage | HBO - HBO.com</title><snippet>The official website for Silicon Valley on HBO, featuring videos, images, schedule information and episode guides.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley tech news, reviews and insights ...</title><snippet>The latest technology news from Silicon Valley's biggest companies and most influential executives, from the San Jose Mercury News.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Zemsta nerda - nowy serial 'Silicon Valley' - Gazeta Wyborcza</title><snippet>8 kwi 2014 - "Silicon Valley" - nowy serial HBO, co samo w sobie jest znakiem jakości - podejmuje znajomy temat amerykańskiego mitu "od pucybuta do ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley Acceleration Center (SVAC) - WPHI ...</title><snippet>29 sty 2014 - Silicon Valley Acceleration Center (SVAC). Wydział Promocji Handlu i Inwestycji Ambasady RP w Waszyngtonie D.C. (WPHI), we współpracy z ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley | Facebook</title><snippet>Silicon Valley. 93438 likes · 8532 talking about this. Mike Judge brings his irreverent brand of humor to HBO in this new comedy series. "Silicon...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon's Valley's Brutal Ageism | New Republic</title><snippet>23 mar 2014 - A behind-the-scenes report from the most ageist place in America: Silicon Valley.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley . American Experience . WGBH | PBS</title><snippet>The history of Silicon Valley, from PBS and American Experience. In 1957, decades before Steve Jobs dreamed up Apple or Mark Zuckerberg created Facebook ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley Contemporary</title><snippet>The Official International Contemporary &amp; Modern Fine Art Fair of Silicon Valley.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Microsoft Research Silicon Valley - Microsoft Research</title><snippet>Located in Mountain View, California, Microsoft Research Silicon Valley was founded in August 2001 and employs over 75 researchers. The lab's primary focus ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>OPEN Silicon Valley</title><snippet>There are a lot of young college grads looking for advice and guidance from the experienced Silicon Valley corporate professionals.” - Yasser Khan, Attendee &amp; ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Joint Venture - Silicon Valley Network</title><snippet>Joint Venture Silicon Valley: Established in 1993, Joint Venture Silicon Valley provides analysis and action on issues affecting our region's economy and quality ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley Community Foundation: Home</title><snippet>An independent, public benefit organization providing grants for various local needs. Also serves as a convener and catalyst, leveraging new funds and creating ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley Campus - Carnegie Mellon University</title><snippet>Graduate degrees and research for Silicon Valley professionals and executives.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley Bank - UK Home</title><snippet>Silicon Valley Bank provides unique and flexible financial solutions to the most innovative and entrepreneurial companies worldwide.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley Bank - SVB.com</title><snippet>Provides diversified financial services to emerging growth and mature companies in the technology, life science, private equity and premium wine markets.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Welcome to the Silicon Valley Index website!</title><snippet>The Silicon Valley Index has been telling the Silicon Valley story since 1995. Released early every year, the Index is based on indicators that measure the ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley Creates (formerly Arts Council Silicon Valley ...</title><snippet>Silicon Valley Creates is a private, nonprofit arts organization dedicated to improving the quality of life for Santa Clara County residents by creating and fostering ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>VMUG : Silicon Valley VMUG User Conference -- Event ...</title><snippet>Thank you to those who attended the 2014 Silicon Valley VMUG User Conference. We hope you enjoyed the conference and gained valuable insights into ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley Gives: Home</title><snippet>2014 Silicon Valley Community Foundation * 2440 West El Camino Real, Suite 300 | Mountain View, CA 94040 tel: 650.450.5400 | svgives@siliconvalleycf.org.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Product Camp Silicon Valley</title><snippet>The Seventh Annual Product Camp Silicon Valley for Product Managers and Product Marketing Managers.</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Sustainable Silicon Valley: Front Page</title><snippet>Carbon pollution affects all of us whether in Silicon Valley or the East Coast. President Obama's Climate Action Plan is designed to begin slowing down the ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Launch Silicon Valley 2014 | -</title><snippet>The Group winners scored fantastic prizes provided by Group sponsors, as well as one-on-one meetings with Silicon Valley's top VCs, angels, corporate venture ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Breakthrough Silicon Valley</title><snippet>Breakthrough Silicon Valley launches high potential, underserved middle school students on the path to college and inspires high school and college students ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley Gives: Welcome to</title><snippet>The generosity of our donors and sponsors made our first Silicon Valley Gives event an incredible success. Our community united to raise $7,935,704 in 24 ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>SQLSaturday #276 - Silicon Valley 2014</title><snippet>Welcome to SQLSaturday Silicon Valley. March 15, 2014. Microsoft Technology Center, Mountain View, CA. SQLSaturday was a free, one-day learning event ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
<document><title>Silicon Valley Pad</title><snippet>“Our company has been a very happy customer of Silicon Valley Pad since 2008...” Michael Shraybman. Cogniance CEO. “After having looked at The Pad there ...</snippet><url>http://</url></document>
</searchresult>